https://www.ceilingfan.com/v/policy.htm

Room Size
Great Rooms (65" and up)
Large Rooms (60" - 64")
Standard Rooms (45" - 59")
Small Rooms (40" - 44")
Small Spaces (29" - 36")
Call Center Hours
(PST) Mon-Fri: 7am - 6:00pm | Sat: 7am - 5pm | Sun: 9am - 5pm
(EST) Mon-Fri: 10am - 9:00pm | Sat: 1pm - 8pm | Sun: 3pm - 8pm
Room Size
Great Rooms (65" and up)
Large Rooms (60" - 64")
Standard Rooms (45" - 59")
Small Rooms (40" - 44")
Small Spaces (29" - 36")
Payment Policy
Although we take your credit card number at the time you place your order, we only make sure the funds are there but do not actually charge it until your order has shipped. Due to high volume of our business, in some instances we may be out of the product you've ordered. When this happens, we will let you know the item is on back order and you can choose to wait until it is in stock or cancel your order. Due to unforseen circumstances with stock and shipping, we do not recommend you scheduling an electrician before receiving your products. We can not be held liable for extra electrician fees due to shipping errors by the carriers or any other reason.
Price Match Policy
CeilingFan.com strives to provide quality products and services at competitive prices. In the event you find a competitor with lower prices, CeilingFan.com will be more than happy to price match under these conditions:
1. Price match is for the total shipped price*
2. Matching a price does not violate the manufacturers resale policy.
3. If the product has been discontinued, we reserve the right to not price match.
4. Blowout sale items are not applicable.
5. Price matching does not apply to Minka Aire products.
Warranty
CeilingFan.com is a dealer only. Products sold by CeilingFan.com are not manufacturered by CeilingFan.com and therefore are not warrantied by CeilingFan.com. The products may, however, be covered by each manufacturer's warranty, service, and support policy (if any). CeilingFan.com assigns and passes through to the customer any warranty of the manufacturer, and customer acknowledges they shall have a recourse only under such warranties and against the manufacturer of the products. CeilingFan.com makes no representation or express warranty with respect to the product except those stated in this document. CeilingFan.com disclaims all other warranties, express or implied, as to any such product, including and without limitation, the implied warranties of mechantability and fitness for a particular purpose, and any implied warranties arising from statute, trade usage, course of dealing, or course of performance. CeilingFan.com is dedicated in helping the customer utilize the manufacturer's warranty to their fullest extent. However, shipping is still the customer's responsibility. No replacement product will be shipped without the original merchandise returned or a deposit equating to the cost of the product.
Limitation Of Liability
In all circumstances CeilingFan.com maximum liability is limited only to the purchase price of the product sold. CeilingFan.com shall not, under any circumstances, be liable upon a claim or action in contract, tort, indemnity or contribution, or other claims relating to the products it sells which exceeds this liability limit. CeilingFan.com shall not be liable for third party claims for damages against the customer, or for malfunction, delays, interruption of service, loss of business, loss or damage to exemplary damages, whether or not CeilingFan.com is apprised of the possibility of such claims or damages.
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for Web Pages, Newsletters, Discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by CeilingFan.com The following discloses our Privacy Policy.
Incomplete Shipments
In the event your shipment is incomplete or missing parts, please notify your salesperson as soon as possible. Customers have a 30-day period to claim any missing product(s). Beyond the 30 day period, any missing product becomes the customer's responsibility.
Information that CeilingFan.com Collects When You Purchase
If you are purchasing something from CeilingFan.com, we need to know your Name, E-Mail Address, Mailing Address, Credit Card Number & Expiration Date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This infromation may also be used by us to notify you of related product and services. Credit Card & E-Mail information will NOT be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express permission.
In the future, CeilingFan.com will deploy a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between your and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information.
Wherever CeilingFan.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.
What Else You Should Know About Your Privacy Online
CeilingFan.com web site may contain hyperlinks to other Web Sites. CeilingFan.com may also contain advertisements of third parties. CeilingFan.com is not responsible for the privacy practicies or the content of such Web Site or Advertisers. CeilingFan.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide CeilingFan.com with the Web Sites to which CeilingFan.com links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although CeilingFan.com may share aggregate data with such Web Sites (such as how many people use our site).
Please check with thoser sites to determine their Privacy Policy.
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclone personal information online - for example through E-Mail, Discussion Lists, Or Elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.
Your Consent To This Agreement
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by CeilingFan.com as specified above. If we decide to change our pirvacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We reserve the right to make modifications to this policy at anytime.
When you purchase from us, it is hereby stated that you agree with our polices above.
Please note that your use of CeilingFan.com Web Site is governed by our Legal Notice
Contact Us at 1-877-332-6700 (Toll Free)
Copyright © 1996-2019 CeilingFan.com. All Rights Reserved. All trademarks and brands are property of their respective owners.
F.A.Q.
1-877-332-6700 (Toll Free)
877-332-6700
X
